[
{"question":"acheter",	"answer":"köpa"},
{"question":"adorer",	"answer":"beundra"},
{"question":"aimer",	"answer":"älska"},
{"question":"arroser",	"answer":"vattna"},
{"question":"bavarder","answer":"snacka"},
{"question":"chanter",	"answer":"sjunga"},
{"question":"chercher",	"answer":"leta"},
{"question":"créer",	"answer":"skapa"},
{"question":"croire",	"answer":"tro"},
{"question":"cuisiner",	"answer":"laga mat"},
{"question":"danser",	"answer":"dansa"},
{"question":"demander",	"answer":"fråga/be om"},
{"question":"devenir",	"answer":"bli"},
{"question":"donner",	"answer":"ge"},
{"question":"écouter",	"answer":"lyssna"},
{"question":"entendre",	"answer":"höra"},
{"question":"entourer",	"answer":"omringa"},
{"question":"entrer",	"answer":"gå in"},
{"question":"éternuer",	"answer":"nysa"},
{"question":"étudier",	"answer":"studera"},
{"question":"fermer",	"answer":"stänga"},
{"question":"gagner",	"answer":"vinna, tjäna"},
{"question":"lever",	"answer":"lyfta"},
{"question":"lutter",	"answer":"strida, kämpa, slåss"},
{"question":"monter",	"answer":"gå upp, stiga på"},
{"question":"nager",	"answer":"simma"},
{"question":"parler",	"answer":"prata"},
{"question":"partager",	"answer":"dela"},
{"question":"partir",	"answer":"åka iväg"},
{"question":"planter",	"answer":"plantera"},
{"question":"pleurer",	"answer":"gråta"},
{"question":"porter",	"answer":"bära, ha på sig"},
{"question":"prier",	"answer":"be"},
{"question":"promener",	"answer":"promenera"},
{"question":"ramasser",	"answer":"samla, plocka"},
{"question":"ranger",	"answer":"ordna, städa"},
{"question":"rater",	"answer":"missa, misslyckas"},
{"question":"regarder",	"answer":"titta"},
{"question":"reposer",	"answer":"vila"},
{"question":"rester",	"answer":"stanna"},
{"question":"retourner",	"answer":"komma tillbaka"},
{"question":"rire",	"answer":"skratta"},
{"question":"sauter",	"answer":"hoppa"},
{"question":"sentir",	"answer":"känna"},
{"question":"sourire",	"answer":"le"},
{"question":"tenir",	"answer":"hålla"},
{"question":"travailler",	"answer":"arbeta"},
{"question":"trouver",	"answer":"hitta"},
{"question":"vendre",	"answer":"sälja"},
{"question":"voyager",	"answer":"resa"}
]